cksinfo.com 2019-09-24

# Privacy Policy - AllFreeClipart.com

This notice provides AllFreeClipart.coms policy regarding the nature, purpose, use and sharing of any information collected via this Web site. 

Submitting information is strictly voluntary. By doing so, you are giving AllFreeClipart.com your permission to use the information for the intended purpose. 

There are several types of information we collect. These include: 

Automatically Collected Information  
We collect and temporarily store certain technical information about your visit for use in site management and security purposes. This information includes:   
The date and time you access AllFreeClipart.com  
The URLs of the pages you visit  
The Internet domain from which you access AllFreeClipart.com.  
The IP address from which you access AllFreeClipart.com  
The type of browser used to access our site.  
The operating system used to access our site.  
If you visited this Web site from another Web site, the URL of the forwarding site.  
This information is only used to help us make our site more useful for you. With this data we learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. 

Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are retained temporarily as required for security and site management purposes only. 

Cookies  
AllFreeClipart.com Web sites may use session cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through the site, or to allow you to customize your preferences for interacting with the site. 

At no time is your private information, whether stored in persistent cookies or elsewhere, shared with third parties who have no right to that information. If you do not wish to have session or persistent cookies stored on your machine, you can turn them off in your browser. 

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads). 

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose. 

Third party ad-serving by Google:

Google serves ads on this site, and certifies vendors for third party ads. You can find a list of these vendors and ad networks here - [https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/94149)

You may visit those websites to opt out of cookies (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). 

You can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/>

For more information on the types of cookies used by Google, go to the site "Types of cookies used by Google," located at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/types>, or any other URL Google may provide from time to time. For more information on Google Analytics, and how it collects and processes data visit the site "How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or Apps," located at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>. 

**How Your Information May Be Used**

We may use the information collected in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the Website;
  * To create your account, identify you as a user of the Website, and customize the Website for your account; 
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each email promotion will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

**Rights Related To Your Personal Information**

Opt-out - You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us using the email address below. 

Amend - You may contact us to amend or update your personal information. 

Forget - In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to the email address below. 

Access - You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to webmaster@allfreeclipart.com. 

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law. 

Personal Information  
If you choose to provide us with personal information, through such methods as completing a form or sending us an email, we will use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information or services you have requested. 

Accessibility Statement  
We continually strive to ensure the pages on this Web site are accessible to individuals with disabilities in accordance with Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act. If you have any difficulty viewing any page with adaptive technology, please contact the webmaster. 

Linking Policy and Disclaimer of Endorsement  
AllFreeClipart.com links to many Web sites. AllFreeClipart.com provides links to these sites as a service to our users. The presence of a link is not a AllFreeClipart.com endorsement of the site. 

When users follow a link to an outside Web site, they are leaving AllFreeClipart.com and are subject to the privacy and security policies of the owners/sponsors of the outside Web site(s). AllFreeClipart.com is not responsible for the information collection practices of those sites. 

**Contact Us** You may contact us at: webmaster@allfreeclipart.com
